Alexander McKerrow

Full Stack Software Developer

Queenstown, Otago, NZ 02041911568 mckerrow4@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/alexandermckerrow github.com/macakz

About Me

Software development for me is a passion that keeps me up at night, and gets me up in the morning. My love for building and creating whilst solving problems is what drives me with every new project.

I started my coding journey on codecademy 2 years ago, however with a full-time job, I wasn't getting enough hours on the keys a week to progress and develop my skills further and faster. This is why I joined Dev Academy and quickly I was able to see that with dedication and perseverance, software development is a highly rewarding field. Due to the intense and fast paced work environment I soon became proficient in the front-end and backend of software development. Skills and technologies that I use: HTML, CSS, JS, React, Redux, Data Operations with SQL (CRUD), Firebase, GIT, Node, TDD, E2E Testing (Playwright) and CI/CD. However, what I valued most out of the bootcamp was the skill to adapt and take on new concepts quickly with a thorough understanding. Our final group project led us to building a mobile app. Throughout the Bootcamp we had only focused on web apps, we had to adapt our learnings to React Native / Expo. This proved to be a large undertaking in the space of a week, but we were able to produce a digital loyalty card app.

I'm excited to use everything I have learned throughout my bootcamp in a working environment. I am currently working on some freelance projects whilst trying to develop my skills further, such as learning TypeScript . I'm determined and have the ability to work autonomously, but love gaining good working relationships with others.

Interests

- Snowboarding
- Travel
- Basketball
- ❖ DNB

EXPERIENCE

Enspiral Dev Academy, Auckland, New Zealand

Full Stack Development
Jan 2021 - May 2021

YOUI, Auckland, Auckland, New Zealand

Sales Advisor Feb 2020 - Dec 2020

Victor Contractors, Auckland, New Zealand

Apprentice Electrician
Jan 2016 - Oct 2018

Nita Lake Lodge, Whistler, BC, Canada

Night Auditor / Night Manager
Oct 2014 - Oct 2015

Sofitel Queenstown, Queenstown, New Zealand

Concierge
Oct 2012 - Oct 2013

EDUCATION

Enspiral Dev Academy, Auckland, New Zealand

Full Stack Development Jan 2021 - May 2021

International College of Management Sydney, Manly, NSW, Australia

Bachelor of Business Management
Jan 2014 - Aug 2014

Queenstown Resort College, Queenstown, New Zealand

Diploma of Hospitality Management
Jan 2012 - Oct 2013